klikot.com 2015-12-31

# Klikot | Terms Of Service

    **Klikot - Privacy Policy**
    
     version  ( **1-9-2008** )

    We respect your privacy. This policy explains the accepted privacy practices for Our online social network 
    at [www.Klikot.com](http://www.klikot.com/) ("Klikot"). It describes the personal information that We collect directly from you, the 
    information automatically logged when you use Klikot, the ways We retain, use and disclose the information, 
    and your rights with respect to such information. This policy is incorporated to the Klikot's 
    Terms of Use (the "Terms", or the "Terms of Use"). 
    
    **_Personal information that We collect_**
    We do not knowingly collect your personally identifiable information without your consent. When you register 
    with Klikot and set up your personal account, We will ask you to provide Us with certain contact and personal 
    details such as your name and e-mail address, in order to enable you to login to Klikot. Additionally, certain 
    Services on Klikot may require you to furnish Us with relevant information in order to complete the respective 
    Service. We will explicitly state the information We require on the relevant web pages. We may collect further 
    information when you use any of the Services on Klikot. For example, we may record the frequency and scope 
    of your use of the services, the duration of your sessions, the web pages that you visit, information that you 
    read, content that you use or create, advertisements that you view or click on, your communications with other 
    users and third parties on Klikot, the Internet protocol (IP) address and the name of the domain that serve you 
    to access Klikot, or any of the Services, and the geographic location of the computer system that you are using 
    to log-in on Klikot. We may automatically gather this information, through the use of log files. If you are registered 
    with Klikot, the information we gather may be anonymous or in some instances personally identifiable. If you are 
    not a registered user, than we will not knowingly make use of any information which personally identifies you, 
    except as specifically indicated in the policy. Further information may be collected when We exchange communications 
    with you, for example, if you submit a request to our customer support, or write to Kliker – your online friend on our 
    behalf or when you contact our designated Copyright Agent. 
    
    **_Personal information that you share_**
    Klikot enables you to upload, distribute, e-mail, disseminate, transmit or otherwise make your content available 
    on Klikot, and to share it with other users. The content that you post, including text and images, may be accessible 
    to other users, according to the personal preferences that you set when you create your personal account, and may 
    appear in search results on Klikot. You must exercise caution and common sense when posting your content, especially 
    any personally identifiable information. At the very least you should demonstrate the same degree of caution as when 
    publishing your content by any means other than the internet.
    
    **_What do We do with your personally identifiable information?_**
    We may use personally identifiable information for the following purposes only:
    
    •	To enable you to use Klikot and to provide you with the Services; 
    
    •	To improve and customize your experience on Klikot; 
    
    •	To provide you with support, handle complaints and collect fees;
    
    •	To send you updates and notices, to provide you with information pertaining to the Services and our services 
    	 elsewhere and to provide you with further marketing and advertising material, subject to your prior indication 
    	 of consent on Klikot. At any time you may opt out of Our mailing lists, by changing your preferences in your
    	 Klikot personal account. In any case, We will not share your personal identifiable details with any advertisers, 
    	 without your explicit consent; 
    
    •	To post your content on Klikot and to facilitate communication between you and us, and between you and 
    	 other users;
    
    •	To enforce the Terms of Use; 
    
    •	To display or publish your relevant personal details when we give you monetary rewards, whether on Klikot, 
    	 the media or any other way.
    
    •	To contact you as and when we believe it to be necessary;
    
    •	To comply with any applicable law and assist law enforcement agencies under any applicable law:
    
    •	To collect fees and debts, and to prevent fraud, misappropriation, infringements, identity thefts and any 
    	 other misuse of Klikot; 
    
    •	to take any action in any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind between you and us, or between you 
    	 and other users or third parties with respect to, or in relation with Klikot; 
    
    **_How do We use aggregated information?_**
    We may use anonymous, statistical or aggregated information on Klikot, including posting, disseminating, transmitting 
    or otherwise communicating or making available such information through Klikot, or to users on Klikot, or to Our suppliers, 
    partners and any other third party, at Our sole discretion, provided however, that such information will not identify you 
    personally and that we will not knowingly, or intentionally use such information to reveal your identity without your consent, 
    under the terms of this Policy. We may also use anonymous, statistical or aggregated information to properly operate Klikot, 
    to improve the quality of the services, to enhance your experience, to create new services, including customized services, to 
    change or cancel existing content or Services and for further internal and statistical purposes. 
    
    **_Sharing information with others_**
    We do not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to third parties for any of their marketing purposes. 
    We may share personally identifiable information with others in any of the following instances, or subject to your 
    explicit consent: 
    
    •	When you use the Services, or when you take part in any content-related activity, or request for a third party's 
    	 service through Klikot, or when you use such service. In these cases, we will share your information only to the 
    	 extent required to facilitate your use of the Services;
    
    •	If We reasonably believe that you have breached Klikot's Terms of Use, or abused your rights to use Klikot, or 
    	 performed any act or omission that we reasonably believe to be violating any applicable law, rules, or regulations. 
    	 We may share your information in these cases, with law enforcement and other competent authorities and with any 
    	 third party, as may be required to handle any result of your wrongdoing;
    
    •	If We are required, or reasonably believe that we are required by law to share or disclose your information; 
    
    •	In any case of dispute, or legal proceeding of any kind between you and us, or between you and other users or third 
    	 parties with respect to, or in relation with Klikot; 
    
    •	In any case where We may reasonably believe that sharing information is necessary to prevent imminent physical 
    	 damage or damage to property; 
    
    •	If We organize the operation of Klikot within a different framework, or through another legal structure or entity, or 
    	 if We are acquired by, or merged with another entity, provided however, that those entities agree to be bound by 
    	 the provisions of this policy, with respective changes taken into consideration;
    
    •	We may also share personally identifiable information with companies or organizations connected, or affiliated 
    	 with Us, such as subsidiaries, sister-companies and parent companies, with the express provision that their 
    	 use of such information must comply with this Policy.
    
    **_Accessing your personal information on Klikot_**
    At any time you may access your account on Klikot and edit, or amend your personal information. If you find that the 
    information on your account is not accurate, complete or updated, than you must make all necessary changes to correct 
    it. Please keep in mind that false, incorrect, or out dated information may prevent you from registering with Klikot and 
    impair Our ability to provide you with Services and to contact you. You are entitled, no more than twice a year, whether 
    by yourself or through a duly authorized proxy, or a legal guardian, and at your own expense, to access your personally 
    identifiable information on Klikot's databases. If you find that the information is not accurate, complete or updated, then 
    you may request to correct, amend or delete such information. We may refuse to comply with your request for various 
    reasons, for example, if We think that deleting certain information might prevent Us from maintaining necessary contact 
    with you, or jeopardize certain activities on Klikot, or harm other users. In any case, We will inform you whether We 
    would comply or refuse to your request. Prior to accessing personal information on behalf of another person, We may 
    ask you to provide Us with a written and duly signed power of attorney, specifically confirming that you are authorized 
    by the personal information's subject, or the subject's legal guardian, to access the information and edit, or amend it. 
    You agree that We may deny you access, if you fail to provide Us with the necessary power of attorney. 
    
    **_Data retention_**
    We reserve the right at all times to review, retain and/or disclose any information as We deem necessary to satisfy 
    any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request. However, by doing so We do not either expressly
    or impliedly endorse, affirm or in any manner assume any responsibility for such communications. 
    
    **_Cookies_** 
    We may use cookies on Klikot. Cookies are packets of information sent by Our servers to your web browser and 
    then sent back by the browser each time it accesses Our servers. The cookies may contain a variety of information, 
    such as the content of search queries, Klikot's pages you have accessed, session durations and IP addresses. 
    We may use cookies for various purposes, such as to save you the need to re-enter your user name and password each 
    time you login on Klikot, to facilitate the use of Services on Klikot, to collect statistical information with respect to the use 
    of Klikot, to verify information, to customize Services on Klikot to your personal preferences and for information security 
    purposes. Some of the Cookies may expire when the session ends and you exit your browser. Other cookies are saved 
    on your computer’s hard drive. If you wish to block our cookies, then please use the help button in your browser and 
    follow the necessary instructions. However, bear in mind that disabling cookies may complicate or even prevent your 
    use of Klikot, or certain features thereof. 
    
    **_Advertising campaigns_** 
    We may permit certain other companies to conduct advertising campaigns on Klikot. The advertisements that you see 
    when accessing Klikot are redirected from the servers of those advertising companies. Some advertisers may use cookies 
    on your computer. The cookies enable them to collect information about websites that you have accessed, advertisements 
    posted on those sites and the advertisements that you have viewed. In this manner advertisers try to customize advertisements 
    to your preferences. The advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies and not to this Policy. If you 
    wish to study the privacy policies of those advertisers you should visit their websites, or contact them directly.
    
    **_Information Security_**
    We implement systems, applications and procedures to secure your personal information, to minimize the risks of theft, 
    damage, loss of information, or unauthorized access or use of information. However, these measures are unable to provide 
    absolute assurance. Therefore, although We take great efforts to protect your privacy, We do not guarantee and you cannot 
    reasonably expect that Klikot and Our databases will be immune from any wrongdoings, malfunctions, unlawful interceptions 
    or access, or other kinds of abuse and misuse, or that your private communications on or through Klikot will remain private. 
    
    **_Changes to this Privacy Policy_**
    We may change and update the terms of this Policy from time to time. We therefore recommend that you read it periodically. 
    All substantial changes that We make to this Policy will be notified on Klikot and take effect 30 days following their initial posting.
